They showed up normal, looking clean The kind of calm I
hadn't seen
Said just a place to crash one night Swear I'll be gone by
morning light
But he overslept and missed his call Said one more night I
've lost it all
They'd been through hell, I gave him a shot But the c
ravings came and he just forgot
I gave you my couch, gave you a break Thought you'd stay
clean for everyone's
sake But you dropped at G when the house went still Now you
're shaking hard and getting
your fill I went to bed, you went to war Shaking our
friendship to its very core
Lauren called, says she's still got hope Jorah's shadow
slipping down a slope
It's a pile of moments you've let slide by While you chase
sleep with a chemical high
They'd come tomorrow if you'd just say when But you're
locked in the arms of your oldest
friend And he don't care if you wake again
I gave you my couch, gave you a break Thought you'd stay
clean for everyone's
sake But you dropped at G when the house went still Now you
're shaking hard and getting
your fill I went to bed and banged the floor
It wasn't smack, it wasn't blow This shit creeps in quiet
and steals the show
Your eyes rolled back, your fists went tight You were
drowning dry in the pale porch like
You said it's GBH or maybe G But you were gone before it's
plain to me
I sat there holding your vacant shell A front row seat in a
private hell
I gave you my couch, gave you a break Thought you'd stay
clean for everyone's sake
But you dropped at G when the house went still Now you're
shaking hard and getting your fill
I went to bed, you went to war Shaking our friendship to
its very core